Alright so why don't we search for something like earthquake deed api.
好吧 那么我们为什么不搜索一下 例如 earthquake data api
Look at this first result, looks pretty good, actually.
看一下第一条结果 看上去竟然非常匹配
It's from the USGS, which is the geological survey.
该条结果来自 USGS 是一份地质勘查文档
&gt;&gt; Yeah the USGS earthquake site is awesome.
— 是的 USGS 地震站点非常好
Since we feel a lot of quakes here in California,
因为加利福尼亚这里经常发生地震
if I ever experience one, I'll usually run over here and try and
如果我遇到一次地震 我会打开这个网站
look up the magnitude and epicenter, and see if other people are feeling it.
尝试查找震级和震中 看看是否有其他人和我一样感到有地震
&gt;&gt; Awesome.
— 非常好
Yeah, it looks super useful.
是的 这个站点看起来超级实用
Although I'm seeing this site here called seismi,
然而 我正在浏览的这个站点称为 SEISMI
which seems to be about visualizing earthquakes.
该站点似乎与地震可视化有关
If I take a look at the API, pretty simple, and
浏览一下 API 相当简洁
seems to have the data we want, too.
似乎同样包含我们需要的数据
What do you think?
你认为怎么样?
&gt;&gt; Seismi's pretty cool, but what it is is a visualization of earthquake data.
— SEISMI 非常棒 它实际上就是对地震数据的可视化处理
Ironically, it's getting its data from the USGS itself.
其实 它的数据均取自 USGS 站点
So given that, I'm going to recommend we just go with the USGS as our API source.
鉴于此 我建议大家仅将 USGS 作为我们的 API 源
&gt;&gt; I didn't know that.
— 我并不知道这回事
But looking at this documentation from the USGS,
但是 看一下这份由 USGS 发布的文档
it looks pretty straightforward and not too hard to read.
看起来相当简单直接 易于理解
Let me scan down here a little bit.
让我们往下浏览一点
Actually, it looks like this query section is really powerful.
事实上 其中的查询部分功能十分强大
There's actually some really interesting queries we could do.
我们其实可以在这里进行一些有趣的查询
It looks like we can search by time, specify date and time ranges for
我们似乎可以按时间查询指定地震发生的日期和时间
earthquakes.
和范围
This looks actually really great.
这看起来真的非常棒
You can actually search for earthquakes based on a geographical
你其实可以基于指定为
region that you either specify as a rectangle.
矩形的地理区域搜索地震
Or yeah, here's a classic one, where you can search for
或者 是的 还有典型的搜索方式 你可以基于
earthquakes based on a radius.
半径范围来搜索地震
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I'd love to restrict the search results to Nevada in the 1960s,
— 是的 我喜欢将该搜索结果限制到 20 世纪 60 年代的内华达州
and see what comes back.
然后看看会得到什么结果
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] Yeah, there was a lot of action going on back then.
— 是的 那时进行了很多运动
&gt;&gt; Well, it looks like we've got the data that we're looking for for
我们好像找到了我们为应用查找的数据
our app, I see depth and magnitude sorting options.
这里有深度和震级 还有分类选项
Seems pretty powerful.
看起来相当全面
I think it'd be a good candidate for the app.
我认为它是应用的有力候选
&gt;&gt; Looks good.
— 看起来不错
I think this API looks solid, and we should give it a try.
我认为 API 看起来很可靠 应该找机会试用一下
&gt;&gt; All right, why don't we do it?
— 是啊 为什么不呢?